## **BRADY HRABOVSKY**

185D Perkins Road Rochester, NY 14623

bsh8645@rit.edu 307·256·9215 people.rit.edu/bsh8645 5960 Klipstein Road Cheyenne, WY 82009

**SUMMARY** 

Apply formal education and cooperative education experiences at a salaried full-time position in the Mechanical Engineering field. Interested in topics such as aerospace design and analysis, controls theory and design, robotics, and process automation. Available to begin upon graduation in May 2018.

**EDUCATION** 

### ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, Rochester, NY

BS/MEng in Mechanical Engineering, expected May 2018 Master's Focus in Controls, Minor in Electrical Engineering

GPA: 3.88/4.0

RIT Honors Program, Outstanding Undergraduate Scholar Award, Kearse Writing Award

**CLEARANCE** 

**SECRET, Obtained summer 2016** 

**PROJECTS** 

#### **Electric Motor Test Stand and Performance Archiving**

Using an Arduino Uno and various IC's/basic electrical circuit components, developed a safe, reliable, and user-friendly method for testing and recording electric motor/propeller performance metrics such as thrust output and power consumption versus throttle input.

#### **Autonomous Control and Tracking of Quadcopter Using OpenCV**

Implemented object tracking using a laptop and webcam along with the OpenCV framework with C++ and JavaScript to autonomously solve kinematic equations to track and control a quadcopter to catch a thrown ball.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Lockheed Martin Corporation, Bothell, WA

#### **Mechanical Engineer Intern**

June 2017 – August 2017

Provided design support for infrared laser counter measure applications, including mechanical aperture design as well as electronics selection. Additionally, utilizing CREO and ANSYS, provided design and structural analysis for contract proposal efforts.

#### Lockheed Martin Corporation, Syracuse, NY

#### **Mechanical Engineer Intern**

June 2016 – August 2016

Employed CREO and ANSYS in support of the Production Hardware team to design and analyze various integration and structural components to be implemented on developing product lines. Teamed up with manufacturing teams to implement improvements to the safety and reliability of current pneumatic test equipment.

#### GE Aviation, Lynn, MA

#### **Logistics Co-op**

June 2015 – December 2015

Supported Logistics Quality Leader to maintain quality control and special quality processes within Lynn logistics. Collaborated with Cell Leaders to implement new processes to increase productivity while maintaining a high level of safety and quality. Increased the efficiency and accuracy of pre-existing metric tracking by utilizing VBA within Excel to remove user error.

# Honors Program at RIT, Rochester Institute of Technology, Rochester, NY

Student Worker

September 2013 – Present

Assist program Director and Assistant Director. Complete monthly procurement card log, maintain monthly expenditure tracking reports, as well as assist in coordination of yearly social events and institution activities.

SKILLS

ProEngineer (CREO), Solidworks, Autodesk Inventor, MATLAB, Microsoft Office, Excel VBA, Arduino IDE, CorelDraw, basic web development, basic ANSYS.

#### **ACTIVITIES**

RIT Aero Design Club

Treasurer April 2014 – Present

Honors Program at RIT

Orientation Mentor

Fall, 2014 - 2017